gridgum.com 2016-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Gridgum

**Gridgum respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information which you provide to us and which we collect about you in connection with your accessing and use of this website and services associated with it.**

Gridgum **DOES NOT** share personal information of any kind with anyone. We will not sell or rent your name or personal information to any third party. Any data that a user, author or business stores via our website is wholly owned by that user, author or business. At any time a user or business is free to take their data and leave, or can simply remove their data from our website.

Gridgum only collects such personal information that is necessary for you to access and use our services. This personal information can include, but is not limited to, full name, email address, phone number, credit card information, and other personal information necessary to generate legal documents. We also use Google Analytics to track and ensure a pleasant user experience is achieved on our website.

Gridgum may release personal information if Gridgum is required to by law or any investigations relating to fraud. We may also use personal information in a manner that does not identify you specifically nor allow you to be contacted but does identify certain criteria about our website’s users in general (such as we may inform third parties about the number of registered users, number of unique visitors, and the pages most frequently browsed).

Please remember that any information you may disclose on public support forums, comments sections or other public places of our websites or the internet, becomes public information. You should be very cautious when deciding to disclose personal information on these public areas.

If you have any questions or require any further information within this policy, click here to contact us.

_Last updated: March 18th, 2014_
